Gregory Siggins

r

408-661-3227



gregory.siggins@gmail.com



11269 Cherry Ave, Cherry Valley CA, 92223

SKILLS

Leadership/supervisory experience

Communication

Teamwork

Flexibility

Detail oriented

EDUCATION

OSHA₃₀

Paramedicine

WestMed University, Santa Clara, CA Graduated February 2018

EMT - B

National University – Santa Clara, CA Graduated April 2014

ABOUT ME

A Full-Stack Web developer who uses previous experience in paramedic-level emergency medicine to bring a detail-oriented, critical-thinking mindset to my coding. Recently earned a certificate from the UCLA Extension Coding Bootcamp, with skills in the MERN stack, HTML/CSS, SQL, and OOP. Known as a problem solver with a knack for JavaScript, my experience coding has ignited a passion for developing concise and well documented code with a responsive and aesthetically pleasing UX. Strong skills in teamwork and communication under challenging conditions and deadlines are just some of the skills I bring to a team. I am excited to bring my problem-solving drive to a fast-paced team who provides an intuitive, aesthetically pleasing, and UX focused product.

EXPERIENCE

Nuclear Imaging Technologist – Insight Diagnostics

Fresno, CA - 05/2020 - 12/2020

Working with clients to administer medications and treatments to patients prior to testing. Traveling to various sites to oversee daily procedures.

- Explained complicated procedures via clear communication to a wide variety of clients.
- Gathered demographics, registered patients into a database system, and screened patients for risk factors.

Paramedic – Riggs Ambulance Service

Merced, CA - 06/2018 - 03/2020

Provided 911 service to the sick and injured. Worked with small teams and supervised larger teams in complex, high stress situations, while coordinating with other agencies.

- Training new-hires in company policies and procedures.
- Directly responsible for team safety using constant risk and hazard analysis.
- Worked within a tactical medical team, coordinating with multiple federal agencies.

EMT – B – Royal Ambulance

Santa Clara, CA - 07/2014 - 01/2016

Worked as a part of a critical care team providing multi-disciplined care with shared goals. Facilitated comprehensive and individualized care to patients.

 Learned how to provide mobile medical transports safely and in accordance with California's Code of Regulations.

TECHNOLOGY SUMMARY

Languages

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- JQuery
- Bootstrap
- Express
- React
- Node.js

Databases

- Mongo
- Mongoose
- SQL
- Sequelize